http://www.interlinerates.com/display.asp?keyPageID=17&page=privacypolicy

Privacy Policy
Online Privacy Policy
InterlineRates.com (Cruise Vacations, Inc.) respects your privacy. InterlineRates.com understands that making purchases online involves a great deal of trust on your part; we take this trust very seriously, and make it our highest priority to ensure the security and confidentiality of the personal information you provide us
Cruise Vacations provides this statement to inform you about the privacy policy for the InterlineRates.com site ("Site") and choices you may make about the way your information is collected and used. This notice may be accessed from throughout the Site.
The InterlineRates.com site is designed so that you may visit it without identifying yourself or revealing your personally identifiable information ("Personal Information"), which can be used to identify, contact or locate you.
How we use the Information you provide
On some InterlineRates.com pages, you may register to receive a periodic e-mail about travel-related offers.
The types of Personal Information collected may include an e-mail address, postal code, name, physical address and credit card account number and expiration date.
From time to time, Cruise Vacations, Inc also may use your Personal Information to provide you with marketing offers or to contact you for the purpose of market research. Cruise Vacations, Inc will give you the opportunity to decline such solicitations and will do everything possible to honor such requests.
InterlineRates.com will NOT sell or lease Personal Information to third parties. Unless InterlineRates.com has your permission or is required by law, it only will share your Personal Information with vendors and other suppliers of products or services to fulfill a purchase request authorized by you.
InterlineRates.com uses data collected online, such as Internet Protocol (IP) addresses and other non-personally identifiable information, in aggregate to analyze trends, administer the Site and gather broad demographic information. The aggregated information will not be associated in any way that can identify you individually. We reserve the right to share aggregated information about users of the Site with parties outside of InterlineRates.com, including vendors and business associates.
Be aware that InterlineRates.com may publish links on the Site that connect to external Web sites, which may collect personal information about you. This statement does not cover privacy practices or policies of Web sites external to InterlineRates.com. We provide this notice so that users can make informed choices about sharing personal information with other Web sites.
It’s your information
InterlineRates.com users are given the opportunity to modify their Personal Information by contacting the customer service department at service@CruiseVacations.net. Users who no longer wish to receive the Boat Notes e-mail newsletter may terminate that services by following the unsubscribe instructions at the end of each e-mail newsletter or by e-mailing a request to service@CruiseVacations.net.
Statement Updates
Cruise Vacations, Inc. may update this policy in the future to address new services that may be added to the Site. Please review the privacy policy from time to time to note revisions. If this policy is changed in a material way, we will post notice of the change on the Site. If any proposed change is unacceptable to you, you may request that your Personal Information be removed.
Security
InterlineRates.com takes precautions to protect users’ Personal Information. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have established reasonable procedures to safeguard and secure the information collected online.
Contact Us
If you have any questions or concerns about this policy, you may contact InterlineRates.com at Info@CruiseVacations.net. We will attempt to respond to your query right away.
Home |
Interline Travel Deals |
Learn More |
Get A Quote |
Interline Community | Interline Blog |
About Us
Site Map | Privacy Policy |
Terms of Use
Copyright © 1999-2020, www.InterlineRates.com. All Rights Reserved.
